<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Service Cims - Park Volunteers" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Citizens volunteer to maintain parks that can't be reached by road. Get notified via Chirper when volunteers are dispatched!" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="Service cims allow buildings and parks to be maintained via cim paths, including sidewalk paths, public transportation, and bike paths." /-->
	<LongDescription>
# Service Cims - Park Volunteers (for now)

Version 1.0.0 of this module is focused solely on the Parks Department. The purpose of this mod is to maintain parks that can't be reached by Parks Department vehicles, either because they exist on remote islands and can only be access via ferry, or because they only are accessible via pedestrian paths. This module will recruit unemployed, teen/adult students, retirees, and criminals to become park volunteers for the day and restore maintenance at parks and clean up it's trash. They will take whatever means of transportation available to them to reach the park.

The Parks Department will announce the volunteer for the day, and the park volunteer will also announce via Chirper, allowing you to click on both the cim and the park. (Thanks to @ruzbeh0. for their awesome CustomChirps module and API).

The cim will show VOLUNTEERING AT {name of park} on his cim info window.

## **A few different variables are adjustable via settings:**
1. Dispatch Interval in minutes - how often we check for parks that need maintaining. (1-60 minutes)
2. Max volunteers per dispatch - up to how many cims (1 per park) we will send out to restore a parks maintenance and clean up it's trash. (1-50)
3. Min Failure Count - how many failures the park must have before it's considered a qualifying park. Parks with a lot of failures most likely aren't being reached by Park Maintenance vehicles. (2-50)
4. Maintenance Threshold (%) - What the park maintenance level must be under to qualify for a park volunteer. (0-70%)

## **Technical notes:**
1. Filters out cims that have jobs, are sleeping, sick, or dead.
2. Returns 10 qualifying cims for each park, and picks the closest one.
3. This park also maintains a list of current park volunteers and parks with park volunteers enroute so that they don't get picked again.
4. Watches for cims that fail their route (usually because of route cost exceeding tolerable)
5. Clears park and cim from list once it's been maintained.
  </LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/10-sc-chirper.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/20-sc-restored-park.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/30-sc-park-needing-maintenance.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/40-sc-park-volunteer-enroute.png" />
  <Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/50-sc-settings.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="75426" DisplayName="I18n Everywhere" Version="1.4.*" />
	<Dependency Id="121812" DisplayName="Custom Chirps" />
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/service-cims.1898234/"/>
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="- Initial Release" />
	<!--<ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog>-->
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/mislabeledgadget/CS2Mod-ServiceCims" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
